

THERESA NEATE

DEVOPS / QA /
DEVELOPER ADVOCACY /
LEADERSHIP

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Theresa Neate is a senior developer advocate, lead quality analyst and test consultant - with several years of leadership experience - who loves lean and agility and advocates for holistic system quality and systems thinking. Please note: I'm NOT a "DevOps Engineer".

ROLE PREFERENCE

- platforms & cloud platform & platform thinking
- ideally, including AWS (or GCP)
- systems & operations
- Head Of, Exec Mgr, VP ... (or their deputy)
- keep my tech skills sharp/sharper
- degree of operations/ networking/ Python/ AWS/ flavours work
- more technology, not less
- support to complete Diploma of Networking (& who knows what next)
- balance of strategy / hands-on / management (will always bring Lead QA thinking to the table too)

CAREER HISTORY

Senior Developer Advocate

REA Group | June 2018 - present

Lead Quality Analyst

REA Group | Feb 2016 - June 2018

Lead Agile QA

Australia Post | Jan 2013 - Jan 2016

Lead Quality Analyst

REA Group | Aug 2012 - Dec 2012

Senior QA Consultant

ThoughtWorks | Aug 2009 - Aug 2012

Senior Tester, Helpdesk, Executive Manager, Team Lead

Various | pre-2000 - 2009

COMPETENCIES

- Leadership
- Technical literacy and strong interest
- A range of technical skills, most at the level of "serious playing" and some at "full time specialist" level (including a range of AWS services, Java, JavaScript, Python, Ruby, Buildkite, Docker, Linux, Selenium, SQL, etc.)
- System thinking
- Strong communication skills
- Public Speaking
- Coaching & Mentoring
- Quality Analysis & Testing

TRAINING & EDUCATION

Diploma of Networking

Swinburne University of Technology (2019)

Graduate Certificate: Business IT

RMIT University (2016)

(withdrawn) Bachelors of IT & Systems

Monash University (2014)

Diploma of IT (General)

Victoria University (2010)

Diploma of IT (Web)

Victoria University (2010)

Diploma of Computer Science

South Africa (pre-2000)

Several short courses & certifications

Including ISTQB, ISEB, PACT, CCNA2, Ethical Hacking (Web Security), etc.

Location: Melbourne Australia

CONTACT DETAILS

Website: https://theresaneate.com **Github**: https://github.com/theresaneate

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/neatet/

Twitter: https://twitter.com/TheresaNeate

theresanmail@icloud.com